Enzo Vezzaro

UI / UX designer and Web developer



enzovezzaro05@gmail.com





Pavia, Italy Open to move



enzovezzaro.com insuladigitalstudio.com





github.com/EnzoVezzaro



Hello, I'm Enzo. I love being creative, exploring and broadening my horizons, create high-quality product and giving stunning user experience to my products. I'm an enthusiast of user interface, experience design, and clean and usable coding.

Experiences

May 2017 - Present

Front-End Developer, UI Designer Eleva.it

Pavia, Italy

January 2016 - Present

Head Developer / Art Director Vapecloudshop.com

Santo Domingo, RD

August 2015 - January 2016

Head Developer Thevapelifestore.com

Hollywood, CA

September 2014 - Present

CEO

InsulaDigitalStudio.com

Creating Web/Native Expiriences with modern web technoligies.

Education

2017 - 2018

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship: Mobile Web

Worldwide

2012 -

Computer Science Degree (in process)

Los Angeles City College

Los Angeles, California

2006 - 2010

Multimedia and Communication Diploma I.P.S. Americo D'Aschio

Vicenza, Italy

Languages

Spanish: Native Italian: Native

Tools

Mac OS X Atom Sketch Adobe Suite Affinity Suite Slack Trello InVision Github

Design Skills

Mobile design Photography Prototype design Web design Responsive design App Design



Development Skills

→ → → HTML, PHP, CSS, SASS, JADE, Gulp, NPM, Bootstrap, Javascript, ¡Query, Firebase, Netlify, Moltin, Git, MySQL, AWS, React (Native) Loading . . .

Hobies













